

ContactInfo

♀JEDDAH- TAIF **♀**DUBAI

\$966564369808 KSA

X Ali98720@windowslive.com

Alooosh1928@gmail.com

Skills

- Asp.Net c# ,Asd.net vb.net,
- Asp.net .NET Core c# and vb
- Sql server from 2005 and up
- ADO.NET AND LINQ TO SQL AND Dapper
- HTML,CSS,JAVASCRIPT,JQuery
- php laravel
- Reazer page
- Mvc page
- Flutter
- Php laravel
- Xamarin forms for Android and IOS app Development
- IIS Configuration Server management
- Software Requirement analysis

Summary

Experienced Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Strong engineering professional skilled in Negotiation, Sales, ASP.NET AJAX, Management, JavaScript , *Xamarin froms*, *Reazerpage,Mvc page* and Design patterns. Projects I had built will be at the end of document.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Applications

2011 - 2015

Skimma Manipal University

Experience

Software Developer (C#), Company: PS (Programs Solution)

August 2013 - August 2015

Duties

- Assessing software requirements
- Analyzing and debuggingcode
- Maintaining the stability of all livesystems
- Design and develop C# web applications
- Design and develop umbracocms website
- Outlining and presenting specifications for all softwarerequirements
- Mentoring team members in development and technical progression
- Writing multiple code and script and ensuring cross browser compliance

Software Developer (C# , VB.NET) , Company : Tri Tech 2015 - 2018

Duties

- 1 Have a discussion with client to know and understand the requirements .
- 2 Analysis the requirements .
- 3 Negotiating with others developers the best way to achieve the gole of building this software .
- 4 Make documents describe the work and the framework we are going to use.
- 5- Split the work between the developers including me.
- 6 Test the software , then review it with client and get the feedback from him .
- 7- The technology we are using : Aps.net (clean architecture = UI -> Applications -> Domain -> Infrastructure) ,Html ,css ,javascript,jquary ,Api,Sql

Software Developer (C#, VB.NET), Company: Global Innovation 21/1/2018 - 15/10/2018

Duties

- 1 Have a discussion with client to know and understand the requirements .
- 2 Analysis the requirements .
- 3 Negotiating with others developers the best way to achieve the gole of building this software .
- 4 Make documents describe the work and the framework we are going to use.
- 5- Split the work between the developers including me.
- 6 Test the software , then review it with client and get the feedback from him .
- 7- The technology we are using : Aps.net (clean architecture = UI -> Applications -> Domain -> Infrastructure) ,Html ,css ,javascript,jquary ,Api,Sql

Software Consultant, Company: Hulool Gatway Consultings from 15/10/2018 to 05/06/2019

Team leader ,Company: Shabakah net from 08/03/2020 to 30/09/2020 Left due COVID-19

Software Developer (C#)Company: Atheer Informatio Systems Technology(Nexen) from 16/01/2021 to 30/08/2022

Freelancer, from 2010 until now included all duties above

Languages

Arabic

English

Some projects I had built:

- * Al Ber Association in Wadi Muharram An advertising website using Embraco.
- * Medicine Charitable Association:

A program on the cloud to manage the beneficiaries of the association's services

A program for managing the pharmacy of the association

A program to manage the distribution and delivery of medicines to beneficiaries

A special program to manage the delivery of medicines to beneficiaries

- An interactive map showing the locations and statuses of the beneficiary's disbursement using Google Maps

A volunteer management program to deliver medicines to beneficiaries

Programs for managing the financial resources development department in the association

A program for managing the human resources department of the association

- An integrated system and portal for the association's beneficiaries to enter and follow up on their requests and the status of their file

An electronic market programmed from scratch to receive donations for beneficiaries linked to an integrated control panel.

- Group text messaging system

A simplified system for managing support tickets between the association and the Software Solutions Corporation

- Dozens of various and complex reports have been completed successfully, thank God Programming the Speck Labbaik application using the Zamrin form with its control panel

- * South Asian Pilgrims Foundation:
- A program for managing the meetings of the Chairman of the Board of Directors
- A program to manage the reception of buses of pilgrims from the airport to the residence (linked to the Ministry of Hajj)
- A program for entering the archive

A program to identify the organization's seasonal employees of more than 1,500 employees

- On the web service to accept data from the institution and the Ministry of Health and Umrah
- A program to manage the shareholders' department in the institution
- And many of the program and pages of the institution and dozens of reports
- * Triple Technology Co
- I was the head of the development team. We built a program to manage schools and students in the Royal Commission in Yanbu Al-Sinaiyah

- * Atheer Information Technology Company
- I work as part of a team to build an integrated ERP program and I am responsible for building the department of inventory and customer management, and the construction of this department has been 80% completed